<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "utf-8"?>
<videogamedata>
    <videogame>
        <name>Minecraft</name>
        <date>18 November 2011</date>
        <genre>Sandbox</genre>
        <metacritic>93</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: The game involves players creating and destroying various types of blocks in a
            three-dimensional environment. The player takes an avatar that can destroy or create blocks, forming
            fantastic structures, creations and artwork across the various multiplayer servers in multiple game modes.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_Minecraft.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Eurogamer Germany</reviewer>
                <date>17 January 2012</date>
                <body>Games like Skyrim or GTA love talk about open worlds, but it seems, that so far only Minecraft has
                    truly embraced this principle. (…) This here is your story, that you simultaneously write and
                    experience. All at your own pace.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>1UP</reviewer>
                <date>21 November 2011</date>
                <body>Meanwhile, Minecraft, with all its flaws and quirks, has already joined Super Mario Brothers,
                    Wolfenstein 3D, and Tetris in the pantheon of games that prototyped an entire genre.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>3DJuegos</reviewer>
                <date>25 November 2011</date>
                <body>Minecraft is a masterpiece. A game that you must try.</body>
                <score>91</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>Grand Theft Auto 5</name>
        <date>17 September 2013</date>
        <genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
        <metacritic>96</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: Los Santos: a sprawling sun-soaked metropolis full of self-help gurus, starlets
            and fading celebrities, once the envy of the Western world, now struggling to stay alive in a time of
            economic uncertainty and cheap reality TV. Amidst the turmoil, three very unique criminals plot their own
            chances of survival and success: Franklin, a street hustler looking for tangible opportunities and serious
            money; Michael, a professional ex-con whose retirement is less rosy than he figured it would be; and Trevor,
            a violent dude driven by the opportunity for a cheap high and his next big score. With options at a premium,
            the crew risks it all in a myriad of daring and dangerous heists that could set them up for life.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_GTA5.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Gameplanet</reviewer>
                <date>20 November 2014</date>
                <body>Grand Theft Auto V for new-gen is without a doubt the best way to experience one of the biggest
                    releases of the last half decade.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>NZGamer</reviewer>
                <date>27 November 2014</date>
                <body>A beautiful, expertly realised world.</body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Quarter to Three</reviewer>
                <date>19 December 2014</date>
                <body>With this latest version, Rockstar’s latest game is no longer just a masterpiece. It’s now a
                    state-of-the-art technical marvel. On many levels, you haven’t seen what videogames can accomplish
                    until you’ve played this version Grand Theft Auto V.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>Animal Crossing: New Horizons</name>
        <date>20 March 2020</date>
        <genre>Simulation</genre>
        <metacritic>90</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: If the hustle and bustle of modern life’s got you down, Tom Nook has a new
            business venture up his sleeve that he knows you’ll adore: the Nook Inc. Deserted Island Getaway Package.
            Sure, you’ve crossed paths with colorful characters near and far. Had a grand time as one of the city folk.
            May’ve even turned over a new leaf and dedicated yourself to public service. But deep down, isn’t there a
            part of you that longs for…freedom? Then perhaps a long walk on the beach of a deserted island, where a rich
            wealth of untouched nature awaits, is just what the doctor ordered. Peaceful creativity and charm await as
            you roll up your sleeves and make your new life whatever you want it to be. Collect resources and craft
            everything from creature comforts to handy tools. Embrace your green thumb as you interact with flowers and
            trees in new ways. Set up a homestead where the rules of what goes indoors and out no longer apply. Make
            friends with new arrivals, enjoy the seasons, pole-vault across rivers as you explore, and more.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_ACNH.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>GameSkinny</reviewer>
                <date>8 April 2020</date>
                <body>The latest Animal Crossing is also the best, full of life, charm, and near-endless ways to make
                    your very own island paradise.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Multiplayer.it</reviewer>
                <date>16 March 2020</date>
                <body>New Horizons is the crown jewel in the beloved Animal Crossing franchise: Nintendo managed to
                    surpass every expectation by refining the gameplay with a plethora of features which improve
                    visuals, quality of life and customization.
                </body>
                <score>95</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Slant Magazine</reviewer>
                <date>12 April 2020</date>
                <body>By consolidating so much power in your hands, the game threatens to upend the Animal Crossing
                    vision of community living.
                </body>
                <score>70</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>Wii Sports</name>
        <date>19 November 2006</date>
        <genre>Sports</genre>
        <metacritic>76</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: Tennis (1-4 players): Players grab the controller like a racket and swing – the
            game will register forehands, backhands, volleys, lobs, slices, spin and power depending on how fast the
            user swings and at what angle. Don't worry about moving around the court to get to the ball – the game
            automatically moves players into position. Baseball (1-2 players): Grip the controller like a bat and swat
            fastballs out of the park in a home run derby. Timing and bat speed will make all the difference between
            going yard and whiffing, so keep an eye on the ball and swing for the fences. In the two-player game, one
            player pitches and the other bats. Golf (1 player): Step up to the tee, hold the controller like a golf club
            and swing naturally to smack the ball onto the green. The harder players swing the club, the farther the
            ball will fly, so be sure to take some practice swings before going for the pin. After reaching the green,
            line up putts carefully, practice the stroke and try to hole out. [Nintendo]
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_WiiSports.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>GamePro</reviewer>
                <date>N/A</date>
                <body>We can't help but enjoy the fact that we're getting a solid sports experience for nothing. It's
                    definitely more fun in groups and won't have a great deal of longevity, but anyone who doesn't find
                    at least some fun in Wii Sports has a heart of coal.
                </body>
                <score>85</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>PALGN</reviewer>
                <date>N/A</date>
                <body>A very solid first effort for the Wii, and provides just a taste of what is, and what will be,
                    great about the Wii console. Pick it up, play it and have fun. Very nice.
                </body>
                <score>75</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Console Gameworld</reviewer>
                <date>N/A</date>
                <body>Despite control issues Wii Sports is probably one of the only launch titles that offers so much
                    fun from such a small package.
                </body>
                <score>60</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>PUBG: Battlegrounds</name>
        <date>20 December 2017</date>
        <genre>TPS</genre>
        <metacritic>86</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: PLAYERUNKNOWN'S BATTLEGROUNDS is a last-man-standing shooter being developed
            with community feedback. Players must fight to locate weapons and supplies in a massive 8x8 km island to be
            the lone survivor. This is BATTLE ROYALE.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_PUBG.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>IBTimes UK</reviewer>
                <date>19 February 2018</date>
                <body>The enormity of PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds' success will have surprised even its developers.
                    This is a shooter that didn't invent the Battle Royale genre in gaming, but which certainly
                    perfected it to the point that it found a massive, massive audience. With more than 30 million
                    copies sold, PUBG is a bona fide phenomenon with an influence that will be felt in the industry for
                    years to come.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Metro GameCentral</reviewer>
                <date>22 December 2017</date>
                <body>PUBG is one of the best multiplayer experiences of the generation, and this is the best version of
                    it so far – even if it’s still a work in progress.
                </body>
                <score>90</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>GameCritics</reviewer>
                <date>29 January 2018</date>
                <body>Despite how many technical and design issues it has now, and regardless of however irrelevant it
                    may be in a few years, PUBG is revelatory, and will always hold a special place in my heart.
                </body>
                <score>70</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>New Super Mario Bros</name>
        <date>15 May 2006</date>
        <genre>Platformer</genre>
        <metacritic>89</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: The first new 2D Mario platformer since Super Mario World has arrived. Boasting
            "incredible" 3D graphics to accompany classic 2D gameplay, this fast-paced adventure will have Mario fans
            cheering as they make their way over fields, under water, through castles and into the air. New and familiar
            enemies are everywhere, not to mention "mind-blowing" challenges made possible by the dual screens of the
            Nintendo DS. Not only that, but players can link wirelessly with a friend to play as both Mario and Luigi in
            multiplayer mode. [Nintendo]
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_NSMB.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Computer Games Magazine</reviewer>
                <date>September 2006</date>
                <body>
                    Nintendo sweetened the pot with what feel like dozens of mini-games, and you're liable to find two
                    or three that can hold your attention.
                </body>
                <score>60</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>RewiredMind</reviewer>
                <date>N/A</date>
                <body>
                    As pure a game as you could ever wish to play. Adrenaline, frustration, addiction and the largest
                    hunk of retro gaming pleasure that you could purchase. If you own a DS, and you don’t even give this
                    a chance, you might as well get your consoles listed on eBay. Give up. Buy it. Now.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Digital Entertainment News</reviewer>
                <date>N/A</date>
                <body>
                    New Super Mario Bros. is a solid platformer and a nice homage to the Mario series, but it's not
                    Mario's big return to 2D gameplay like everyone thought it would be.
                </body>
                <score>84</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>Mario Kart 8 Deluxe</name>
        <date>29 May 2014</date>
        <genre>Racing</genre>
        <metacritic>92</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: Race and battle your friends in the definitive version of Mario Kart 8. Hit the
            road with the definitive version of Mario Kart 8 and play anytime, anywhere! Race your friends or battle
            them in a revised battle mode on new and returning battle courses. Play your friends in local wireless
            multiplayer with up to 8 players.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_MK8D.jpeg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Gaming Age</reviewer>
                <date>16 May 2017</date>
                <body>Much of this will seem like a given to Switch owners, but it's still completely relevant in terms
                    of what validates picking up this version of Mario Kart 8. It's not only the "complete" and current
                    experience, but one transformed by its hardware. Mario Kart 8 Deluxe is the definitive version as
                    we're likely to know it from now on, and thanks to the nature of the Switch, it's worth every penny.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>GameCrate</reviewer>
                <date>3 May 2017</date>
                <body>Mario Kart 8 Deluxe is the definitive Mario Kart experience. It’s got the most complete roster of
                    characters, tons of tracks, a litany of game modes, and an ultra-polished presentation mixed with
                    pitch-perfect gameplay. A must play for all Switch owners.
                </body>
                <score>90</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Power Unlimited</reviewer>
                <date>19 October 2017</date>
                <body>You could see Mario Kart 8 Deluxe as an easy port, because it is to a certain extent. But it would
                    be silly to disregard the ultimate fun this kart experience offers because of this. If you have a
                    Nintendo Switch, Mario Kart 8 Deluxe is an essential purchase you will play for over three years and
                    never regret buying.
                </body>
                <score>85</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>Overwatch</name>
        <date>24 May 2016</date>
        <genre>FPS</genre>
        <metacritic>91</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: Overwatch is a highly stylized team-based shooter set on earth in the near
            future. Every match is an intense multiplayer showdown pitting a diverse cast of soldiers, mercenaries,
            scientists, adventurers, and oddities against each other in an epic, globe-spanning conflict.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_Overwatch.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>GameSpot</reviewer>
                <date>24 May 2016</date>
                <body>It's that intoxicating path of discovery that makes Overwatch so varied, so rewarding, and
                    ultimately another seminal release from developer Blizzard. Overwatch is an intelligent cascade of
                    disparate ideas, supporting one another, pouring into one another, and coiling around themselves as
                    they flow into the brilliant shooter underneath.
                </body>
                <score>90</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>The Daily Dot</reviewer>
                <date>27 May 2016</date>
                <body>If you are a first-person shooter fan generally, and if you enjoy team-based FPS play
                    specifically, not at least trying Overwatch feels criminal. Blizzard always imparts a deep sense of
                    holistic quality into its games, and Overwatch is no exception.
                </body>
                <score>90</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>PC Invasion</reviewer>
                <date>6 June 2016</date>
                <body>Blizzard has created a solid team FPS but right now it's light on content.
                </body>
                <score>70</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>Pokemon Fire Red</name>
        <date>7 September 2004</date>
        <genre>RPG</genre>
        <metacritic>81</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: Pokémon Fire Red adds more content and features to one of the first Pokémon
            games ever released. In this version of the classic role-playing game, you can collect all of the monsters
            from different Pokémon installments, including Ruby, Sapphire, and Colosseum. The game comes with a wireless
            adapter, which lets you connect with your friends' Game Boy Advances to chat, trade Pokémon, and participate
            in battles. Other new features include a tutorial mode, a recap system, minigames, and more.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_PokemonRed.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>IGN</reviewer>
                <date>N/A</date>
                <body>Once again, the Pokemon crew create a game that works extremely well for the handheld market. It
                    doesn't have quite the same variety as "Ruby/Sapphire," but it's still incredibly satisfying.
                </body>
                <score>90</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Gamers Europe</reviewer>
                <date>N/A</date>
                <body>I can't help but shake the feeling that Nintendo cut corners on this game – with both the engine
                    and the storyline already made – and this drags the score down.
                </body>
                <score>80</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Cheat Code Central</reviewer>
                <date>N/A</date>
                <body>The new additions don't add up to more than what we call an expansion pack for a PC game.
                </body>
                <score>50</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>Red Dead Redemption 2</name>
        <date>26 October 2018</date>
        <genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
        <metacritic>97</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: Developed by the creators of Grand Theft Auto V and Red Dead Redemption, Red
            Dead Redemption 2 is an epic tale of life in America’s unforgiving heartland. The game’s vast and
            atmospheric world also provides the foundation for a brand new online multiplayer experience. America, 1899.
            The end of the Wild West era has begun. After a robbery goes badly wrong in the western town of Blackwater,
            Arthur Morgan and the Van der Linde gang are forced to flee. With federal agents and the best bounty hunters
            in the nation massing on their heels, the gang has to rob, steal and fight their way across the rugged
            heartland of America in order to survive. As deepening internal fissures threaten to tear the gang apart,
            Arthur must make a choice between his own ideals and loyalty to the gang that raised him. [Rockstar]
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_RDR2.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>XGN</reviewer>
                <date>25 October 2018</date>
                <body>Red Dead Redemption 2 turned out better then we could ever have hoped for. Rockstar knows how to
                    create a vast open world teeming with life, in which Arthur and the Van der Linde gang seek fortune
                    and glory. A new standard for action adventure games has been established.
                </body>
                <score>98</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Jeuxvideo.com</reviewer>
                <date>25 October 2018</date>
                <body>With its amazing open-world, well-written story and deep characters, Red Dead Redemption II is a
                    roller-coaster full of emotions. Controls may feel a bit clunky at times, but still: this is a
                    masterpiece.
                </body>
                <score>95</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Slant Magazine</reviewer>
                <date>25 October 2018</date>
                <body>Red Dead Redemption 2's evocative, often beautiful sense of place exists insofar as it is still
                    convenient to the player, which harms some of the desperation and hardship the game means to convey.
                </body>
                <score>70</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>Terraria</name>
        <date>16 May 2011</date>
        <genre>Sandbox</genre>
        <metacritic>83</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: Terraria offers players a chance to be an action gamer, master builder, a
            collector, and even an explorer.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_Terraria.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>GamePro</reviewer>
                <date>1 June 2011</date>
                <body>Still, Terraria is a great adventure, one of the best sandbox games around, and an absolute steal
                    for ten bucks on Steam. It's well worth checking out for anyone, regardless of how they feel about
                    Minecraft. Despite having one fewer dimension, Terraria hides greater depth than its 3D cousin.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>GameCritics</reviewer>
                <date>24 October 2011</date>
                <body>The open-sandbox creation genre is still in its infancy, and Terraria is a good, solid, and
                    inexpensive entry.
                </body>
                <score>80</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Everyeye.It</reviewer>
                <date>17 June 2011</date>
                <body>An interesting bidimensional twist of the well known Minecraft: Terraria is accustoming and
                    incredibily "deep" (literally).
                </body>
                <score>80</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>The Witcher 3</name>
        <date>19 May 2015</date>
        <genre>RPG</genre>
        <metacritic>93</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: With the Empire attacking the Kingdoms of the North and the Wild Hunt, a
            cavalcade of ghastly riders, breathing down your neck, the only way to survive is to fight back. As Geralt
            of Rivia, a master swordsman and monster hunter, leave none of your enemies standing. Explore a gigantic
            open world, slay beasts and decide the fates of whole communities with your actions, all in a genuine next
            generation format.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_TW3.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Games.cz</reviewer>
                <date>4 June 2015</date>
                <body>The CD Projekt Red surpassed all expectations and they really managed to combine a megalomaniac
                    open world with a strong story. Witcher 3 is a masterpiece, which you will talk to your
                    grandchildren about.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Pure Xbox</reviewer>
                <date>1 June 2015</date>
                <body>If you stick with it until the end, you'll be blown away by its engrossing world, riveting
                    characters, and deep combat system. It's a crowning achievement from the developers, and it's a
                    definite contender for game of the year.
                </body>
                <score>90</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>New York Daily News</reviewer>
                <date>21 May 2015</date>
                <body>The end result is a terrific role-playing game that any fan of Elder Scrolls: Skyrim will love.
                    The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt falls just short of perfection because of those nagging little issues.
                </body>
                <score>80</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>Diablo III</name>
        <date>16 May 2012</date>
        <genre>ARPG</genre>
        <metacritic>88</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: Diablo III picks up the story twenty years after the events of Diablo II.
            Mephisto, Diablo, and Baal have been defeated, but the Worldstone, which once shielded the inhabitants of
            the world of Sanctuary from the forces of both the High Heavens and the Burning Hells, has been destroyed,
            and evil once again stirs in Tristram. Playing as a hero from one of five distinct character classes,
            players acquire powerful items, spells, and abilities as they explore new and familiar areas of Sanctuary
            and battle hordes of demons to safeguard the world from the horrors that have arisen.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_Diablo3.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Polygon</reviewer>
                <date>24 May 2012</date>
                <body>Games this thoughtfully crafted don't happen very often, and the care that Blizzard has taken with
                    Diablo 3 shows in every facet of its design and execution. It might not be perfect, but after 45
                    hours, I'm not sure where it missteps, and after 45 hours, I feel like I've only scratched the
                    surface of what it has to offer. Diablo 3 is almost evil in how high a bar it's set for every PC
                    action RPG to follow, and I wouldn't be surprised to see that bar remain for a very long time.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Armchair Empire</reviewer>
                <date>13 June 2012</date>
                <body>There is absolutely no denying that Diablo III continues to maintain the high artistic standards
                    that it has kept over the years. But the dumbed character and inventory systems, coupled to the
                    ridiculous always-on connection and the breathtaking arrogance of the"you'll play how we tell you to
                    play" attitude makes playing this title a damned shame instead of a hell of a good time.
                </body>
                <score>45</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>GameSpot</reviewer>
                <date>22 May 2012</date>
                <body>There's a good chance you've played games a lot like Diablo III before, and at no point does it
                    dare to surprise you by tinkering with its tried-and-true formula. But it creates such an enticing
                    world and offers up such enjoyable abilities that it makes that formula feel fresh again.
                </body>
                <score>85</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim</name>
        <date>11 November 2011</date>
        <genre>RPG</genre>
        <metacritic>94</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: The next chapter in the Elder Scrolls saga arrives from the Bethesda Game
            Studios. Skyrim reimagines the open-world fantasy epic, bringing to life a complete virtual world open for
            you to explore any way you choose. Play any type of character you can imagine, and do whatever you want; the
            legendary freedom of choice, storytelling, and adventure of The Elder Scrolls is realized like never before.
            Skyrim's new game engine brings to life a complete virtual world with rolling clouds, rugged mountains,
            bustling cities, lush fields, and ancient dungeons. Choose from hundreds of weapons, spells, and abilities.
            The new character system allows you to play any way you want and define yourself through your actions.
            Battle ancient dragons like you've never seen. As Dragonborn, learn their secrets and harness their power
            for yourself.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_TESV.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Armchair Empire</reviewer>
                <date>14 Feburary 2012</date>
                <body>Skyrim is definitely one of the best games of 2011, but if the DLC holds out, it might just be one
                    of the best games of 2012 as well.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>MEGamers</reviewer>
                <date>17 November 2011</date>
                <body>Skyrim is like a music album that has a few tracks that you aren't particularly fond of, but rest
                    of the music is pure aural blliss that you can't help but think of the album as close to perfection
                    as possible.
                </body>
                <score>95</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>PC Games</reviewer>
                <date>16 December 2011</date>
                <body>As expected: an open-world epic with a huge scope and a great atmosphere.
                </body>
                <score>91</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>Super Smash Bros. Ultimate</name>
        <date>7 December 2018</date>
        <genre>Platform Fighter</genre>
        <metacritic>93</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: Inklings from the Splatoon series, as well as returning Smash characters like
            Mario and Link will be making appearances in this classic Nintendo franchise's Switch debut. Faster combat,
            new items, new attacks, new defensive options, and more will keep the battle raging whether you’re at home
            or on the go.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_SMBU.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Power Unlimited</reviewer>
                <date>26 December 2018</date>
                <body>Don't ask me how Nintendo managed to put more than 35 years of experience and love into one
                    product, but they succeeded. Smash Ultimate is not only the ultimate Smash game, the ultimate
                    fighting game, the ultimate party game, and the ultimate collection of videogame nostalgia: it's the
                    ultimate video game. I will continue to play this forever. At least, until Nintendo delivers another
                    sequel.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>XGN</reviewer>
                <date>6 December 2018</date>
                <body>This is the ultimate Super Smash Bros. With an abundance of fighters, stages and modes there is
                    always fun in fighting friends. Even when you're playing by yourself thanks to Classic Mode and
                    World of Light if you play the second one in bite-sized chunks.
                </body>
                <score>97</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Attack of the Fanboy</reviewer>
                <date>10 December 2018</date>
                <body>Super Smash Bros. Ultimate is equal parts greatness and lacking. The sheer wealth of content and
                    great gameplay is commended but there are big holes in what could be a great game.
                </body>
                <score>70</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>The Walking Dead</name>
        <date>24 April 2012</date>
        <genre>Interactive Film</genre>
        <metacritic>89</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: Based on Robert Kirkman's comic book series, The Walking Dead brings to life a
            world devastated by an undead apocalypse and the horrifying choices you're forced to make to survive. Play
            the role of Lee Everett, a convicted criminal, who has been given a second chance at life in a world
            devastated by the undead. With corpses returning to life and survivors stopping at nothing to maintain their
            own safety, protecting an orphaned girl named Clementine may offer you redemption in a world gone to hell.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_TWD.jpeg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>ActionTrip</reviewer>
                <date>23 Janurary 2013</date>
                <body>The Walking Dead represents a jewel in the realm of episodic adventures. This game will shock you.
                    It'll make you cry and curse. One of the most memorable gaming experience we've had in a long time.
                    Don't miss out on it.
                </body>
                <score>96</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>GamingTrend</reviewer>
                <date>7 Janurary 2013</date>
                <body>Overall this game was a unique experience that is not your everyday type of game, but is worth
                    playing and I would suggest this game to almost anyone. It is a game that simply tells a beautiful
                    and tragic story. It sucks you in emotionally and does not let go.
                </body>
                <score>95</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Games.cz</reviewer>
                <date>18 Janurary 2013</date>
                <body>The Walking Dead series offers one of the most intense game story of recent years that is not
                    hardcore on its gamers from the adventure point of view. So relax, seat yourselves and let the
                    zombie-apocalyptic world suck you in.
                </body>
                <score>80</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>Borderlands 2</name>
        <date>18 September 2012</date>
        <genre>FPS</genre>
        <metacritic>89</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: Borderlands 2 advances the distinct blending of FPS and role-playing genres to
            create an evolution of the Role Playing Shooter. Team up with up to 3 other players for 4-player online
            goodness or go old-school with 2-player split-screen couch sharing mayhem as you spend hours leveling up
            your character and equipping them with one of the millions of badass weapons. Borderlands 2 features a new
            array of procedurally generated guns, shields, grenades, artifacts, enemies and more. Choose one of the 4
            new character classes to be taken through a carefully crafted and connected story to all new and surprising
            environments across the living planet of Pandora. Make new friends, arm them to the teeth and fight
            alongside them on your relentless quest for revenge and redemption.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_Borderlands2.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>PC Powerplay</reviewer>
                <date>11 October 2012</date>
                <body>Delivers on every promise of the original, being an instant classic that proudly stands alongside
                    the PC's finest shooters. [Oct 2012, p.62]
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>GamingTrend</reviewer>
                <date>26 September 2012</date>
                <body>If you like piles of guns, lots to do and shoot, and a robust leveling system with a natural coop
                    multi-player aspect and aren't put off by the cel shading, it's a no-brainer.
                </body>
                <score>94</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Absolute Games</reviewer>
                <date>11 October 2012</date>
                <body>Borderlands 2 is awfully simplistic as a first-person shooter, and it's not deep enough for an
                    action/RPG game
                </body>
                <score>66</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>FIFA 18</name>
        <date>29 September 2017</date>
        <genre>Sports</genre>
        <metacritic>84</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: Score incredible goals in FIFA 18 as new movement and finishing animations
            unlock more fluid striking and heading of the ball. All-new crossing controls bring greater options to how
            you send it into the box. Whipped to the spot, arching deliveries, and pinged crosses to the back-stick will
            shake up your attacks in the final third. The biggest step in gameplay, FIFA 18 introduces Real Player
            Motion Technology, an all-new animation system that unlocks the next level of responsiveness and player
            personality. Now Cristiano Ronaldo and other top players feel and move exactly like they do on the real
            pitch. From tiki-taka to high press, new Team Styles put the most recognised tactics of the world's best
            clubs on the pitch in FIFA 18. Enjoy more time and space to read the play through New Player Positioning,
            while improved tactics give players greater options on the ball as teammates exploit space and make new
            attacking runs. [Electronic Arts]
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_FIFA18.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Gaming Age</reviewer>
                <date>29 September 2017</date>
                <body>My opinion on sports games comes down entirely to two factors: how good is the career mode, and
                    how well does it represent the sport. And on both those counts, FIFA 18 delivers in spades.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>PlayGround.ru</reviewer>
                <date>21 September 2017</date>
                <body>FIFA 18 literally launches fireworks into the sky. The game is a real football holiday, and this
                    year it's no less bright than before.
                </body>
                <score>90</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Gameplanet</reviewer>
                <date>29 September 2017</date>
                <body>FIFA 18’s new additions and modes make it the most compelling FIFA experience to date, and the
                    franchise continues to demonstrate why it’s the best football game in the business. Minor complaints
                    aside, FIFA 18 is the biggest and most welcoming football game to date
                </body>
                <score>90</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2</name>
        <date>10 November 2009</date>
        <genre>FPS</genre>
        <metacritic>94</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: Modern Warfare 2 continues the gripping and heart-racing action as players face
            off against a new threat dedicated to bringing the world to the brink of collapse. An entirely new gameplay
            mode which supports 2-player co-operative play online that is unique from the single player story campaign.
            Special Ops pits players into a gauntlet of time-trial and objective-based missions. Rank-up as players
            unlock new Special Ops missions, each more difficult.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_CODMW2.png</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>VideoGamer</reviewer>
                <date>N/A</date>
                <body>It's hard to see the majority of people wanting to play any other multiplayer shooter until the
                    next CoD is released, such is the quality of what's on offer here.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Gamervision</reviewer>
                <date>N/A</date>
                <body>Infinity Ward has managed to outdo themselves with this sequel, a tremendous feat in its own
                    right. If the games of 2009 were stacked up against each other, there’s no question that Modern
                    Warfare 2 would be incredibly close to the apex, fighting viciously for the top spot and, for many
                    people, getting there and continuing upward. This is what gaming is supposed to feel like.
                </body>
                <score>95</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>1UP</reviewer>
                <date>N/A</date>
                <body>The PC version of Modern Warfare 2 is identical to the console versions in almost every way, and
                    that's actually the problem. PC gamers have a certain expectation for online shooters. Removing
                    dedicated server and user mod support from a game that's already $10 more than its predecessor
                    seriously hinders the long term appeal for me.
                </body>
                <score>91</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>

    <videogame>
        <name>The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild</name>
        <date>3 March 2017</date>
        <genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
        <metacritic>97</metacritic>
        <description>Metacritic Summary: Forget everything you know about The Legend of Zelda games. Step into a world
            of discovery, exploration and adventure in The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild, a boundary-breaking new
            game in the acclaimed series. Travel across fields, through forests and to mountain peaks as you discover
            what has become of the ruined kingdom of Hyrule in this open-air adventure. Explore the wilds of Hyrule any
            way you like - Climb up towers and mountain peaks in search of new destinations, then set your own path to
            get there and plunge into the wilderness. Along the way, you'll battle towering enemies, hunt wild beasts
            and gather ingredients for the food and elixirs you'll need to sustain you on your journey.
        </description>
        <boxArt>images/boxArt_BOTW.jpg</boxArt>
        <reviews>
            <review>
                <reviewer>GameGrin</reviewer>
                <date>12 December 2017</date>
                <body>Where it takes mechanics from others in the industry, it improves upon them; where it introduces
                    new ones, you slap your forehead in amazement that it hasn’t been done before. Breath of the Wild is
                    development done right, and damn near the best game you’ll play all year.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>New York Daily News</reviewer>
                <date>7 March 2017</date>
                <body>Despite the stellar story and the absolutely fantastic visuals (aside from some framerate issues
                    on the Switch), it’s this world overflowing with life that will grab and hold your attention for
                    hours upon hours of gaming. As much as this is a story-driven RPG, Breath of the Wild is about its
                    world, a world so vast that you could spend hours upon hours traversing its lands (trust me, I did)
                    before actually making tangible progress in the story...It’s the Zelda game we’ve all been waiting
                    for.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
            <review>
                <reviewer>Polygon</reviewer>
                <date>2 March 2017</date>
                <body>I guess, in the end, it’s not just that Breath of the Wild signals that Zelda has finally evolved
                    and moved beyond the structure it’s leaned on for so long. It’s that the evolution in question has
                    required Nintendo to finally treat its audience like intelligent people. That newfound respect has
                    led to something big, and different, and exciting. But in an open world full of big changes, Breath
                    of the Wild also almost always feels like a Zelda game — and establishes itself as the first
                    current, vital-feeling Zelda in almost 20 years.
                </body>
                <score>100</score>
            </review>
        </reviews>
    </videogame>
</videogamedata>